{
    "subject": "resource/Sandy_Mart\u00ednez",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Villa_Mella,_Dominican_Republic",
    "human_readable": "Sandy Mart\u00ednez was born in Villa Mella, Dominican Republic.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.914452850818634,
            "question": "Is Sandy Mart\u00ednez Dominican?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9111502766609192,
            "question": "Where was Sandy Mart\u00ednez born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6260668635368347,
            "question": "What is Sandy Mart\u00ednez known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5069395303726196,
            "question": "What country is Villa Mella located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41427522897720337,
            "question": "Do you know anything about Sandy Mart\u00ednez's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3528411388397217,
            "question": "Is there a famous landmark in Villa Mella?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26540708541870117,
            "question": "Who are some famous people from the Dominican Republic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2603849470615387,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Villa Mella?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1375378519296646,
            "question": "What is the capital of the Dominican Republic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12458746880292892,
            "question": "What are some popular cultural traditions in the Dominican Republic?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sandy Mart\u00ednez was born in Villa Mella, Dominican Republic.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1089_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the capital of the Dominican Republic?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1089_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Villa Mella?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1089_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous people from the Dominican Republic?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1089_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1089_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1089_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1089_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1089_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1089_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1089_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1089_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1089_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1089_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1089_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The document with file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1089/re-ranker-msmarco/47.txt` mentions that Angel Sandy Mart\u00ednez (also known as Sandy Martinez) was born on October 8, 1970, and the document with file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshamo/ags/dbpedia_1089/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt` mentions a photo of Sandy Martinez taken in Villa Mella, Dominican Republic."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Sandy Mart\u00ednez was born in Villa Mella, Dominican Republic.\" Specifically, the document `52.txt` mentions:\n\n\"Caption: Sandy Martinez, a native of Villa Mella, Dominican Republic signed his first pro deal with the Toronto Blue Jays in 1990 at the age of 19.\"\n\nThis supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}